Claudiu Nichifor

nichifor_claudiu@yahoo.com 07391725122
Full driving license
Fluent in Romanian

16 Gleaves Road Manchester Greater Manchester M30 0FU

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced sales professional with a track record of success in meeting and exceeding sales targets in the telecom sector. Versatile worker with a background in delivery for Amazon and warehouse picking. Skilled in recruitment and sourcing candidates for a variety of positions, particularly for Amazon. A strong team player who is able to work well in fast-paced environments and with a passion for delivering top-notch customer service. I am an excellent communicator and enjoy dealing with people in my chosen career. I am enthusiastic in my work and like to ensure that I get my work completed on time and to the correct deadline where necessary. I am self motivated and able to work well on my own initiative or as part of a team. Portfolio at nichiforclaudiu.com

WORK HISTORY

Customer Advisor May 2023 - Present

Permanent Suits Me Knutsford, Cheshire East

- Compliance
- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Product Knowledge
- Teamwork

Recruitment Resourcer

July 2021 - January 2023

Temporary | Challenge trg Recruitment (formerly PMP Recruitment) | Manchester

- Exceeded recruitment targets
- Conducting interviews
- Handling Database
- Checking right to work

Warehouse Operative

September 2020 - July 2021

Temporary Amazon Manchester

• Recording any damaged, missing or faulty goods.

- Picking goods that have been ordered.
- Managing quality control of goods in and/or goods out.
- Monitored delivery accuracy
- Maintained delivery efficiency
- Communicated with management

Delivery Driver April 2019 - March 2020

Contract Amazon Preston

Warehouse Operative

August 2018 - March 2019

Temporary | Poundland | Wigan

- Met picking quotas
- Picking goods that have been ordered.
- Using computerised systems, barcode scanners and other technology to record goods movement.

D2D Salesman June 2016 - September 2017

Permanent | RCS & RDS | Galati/Romania

- Met sales targets
- Handling Stock
- Handling Database

D2D Salesman August 2015 - April 2016

Permanent Vodafone Galati/Romania

- Met sales targets
- Handling Stock
- Handling Database

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree

Salford University - 2024

Games Design and Production | In Progress

Bachelor's degree

Universitatea "Dunărea de Jos" - 2017

Business Unfinished

International Baccalaureate diploma

Sports Highschool Galati - 2015 Sports

SKILLS

Organisational Skills, Problem Solving, Adaptability, Agile, Attention To Detail, Communication Skills, Customer Focused, Recruitment, C#, Computer Skills, Testing, Team Management, Microsoft Office, Unity Engine, Twine

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

DIY, Football, Martial arts, Music, Video gaming, Design, Travel

REFERENCES

References available on request